teenpornlink.com 2017-07-01

# Privacy Policy

                                                Privacy Policy
Effective: 22-JUL-2014
Domain Cost Club, a California corporation ("DCC" or "we" or "us"), provides registration services for Top
Level Domain (TLD) names in addition to services through www.DomainCostClub.com ("our site" or "the
site") and is committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using its
services.
We collect information from users, Independent Affiliates, and Members of our site (hereafter collectively
“users”). Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use, the Terms of Service, the
Affiliate Agreement, and other published guidelines, we do not release or share personally identifiable
information about users without their permission.
Please note that we review and modify our privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices
are therefore subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure
continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. We will notify registered users
(Members and Affiliates) of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by email to the last known email
addresses of such users. To contact us about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at
abuse@domaincostclub.com.
The information we gather and how we use it
We gather two types of information about the users of our site: non-personally identifiable and personally
identifiable information. When visitors come to our site, we may collect and aggregate non-personally
identifiable information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited, the order in which they
were visited, and which hyperlinks were clicked. Collecting such information involves the logging of IP
addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the site. Although such
information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from the IP address a visitor's Internet
Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.
The non-personally identifiable information we collect helps us, among other things, to monitor our
internal operations, improve our services, identify the most popular areas of our site and determine the
effectiveness of our services and promotional activities. It also helps us make available quality, more
useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of
the users of our site, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of our site.
We provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers, affiliates, and other current and
potential promotional partners.
We may also use cookies which allow us to serve visitors of our site better and more efficiently. Cookies
are small text files placed on a visitor’s computer’s hard drive if permitted by the browser. Cookies,
among other things, make it easier for users to access our site and services, and help us track the pages
that visitors go to, determine the length of time visitors spend at any particular area of the site, and track
the services visitors choose to use. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable
to read data from hard disks, execute any code, send you viruses or destroy your files. For information
on how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser, please refer to the documentation
accompanying your browser.
We do not collect any information that personally identifies you unless you knowingly and willingly
provide it. We explicitly ask for information that personally identifies you. For example, when registering
for a personal account, we require that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information
ranging from basic contact information to payment information to the technical coordinates of your host
servers. Also, you have the option to complete a survey about yourself, your interests and other
information about yourself that will help us, our promotional partners and advertisers offer you value-
added products and services which we believe will be of interest to you.

Although you may not "opt out" of the registration process if you wish to become a Member or an
independent Affiliate, you may choose to "opt out" of receiving promotional materials not directly related
to services provided by us and our affiliates, advertisers, or other business partners. If you do not "opt
out" of receiving such promotional materials, we reserve the right to share any personally identifiable
registration information regarding you to third parties who provide goods or services that we believe may
be of interest to you, whether from outside vendors and/or our own offerings. If you decide that you
would like to discontinue receiving such promotional information, please contact said third parties
directly, or contact us at abuse@domaincostclub.com and we will advise said third parties that you wish
to discontinue receiving their promotional information. Note, however, that we cannot and do not assume
any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use
information received either from DCC or independently. We use personally identifiable information to
operate this site, and we may occasionally inform you by email, telephone, fax (facsimile), text message
(SMS/MMS), and/or social networking sites (e.g. - Facebook, Twitter) of new features, services,
promotions and products available on this site offered by us and our promotional partners. We limit our
own solicitations to those registered users (Affiliates, or Members) who have not "opted out" of receiving
such communications. Our solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly indicate
the sender and provide the customer with a method of "opting out" of receiving future communications
of a similar nature. If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving information from us about
new features, services, promotions and products; or that you would like to reverse a prior opt-out
designation; please contact us at abuse@domaincostclub.com.
We reserve the right to disclose information contained within our access logs concerning any user as we
reasonably feel is necessary to protect our systems or business. Specifically, but without limitation, we
reserve the right to disclose such when a user is in violation of our Terms of Use, Terms of Service (if
applicable), the Affiliate Agreement (if applicable), or other published guidelines, or if a user partakes (or
is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other
court order, and to disclose such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil
subpoenas, discovery requests, and as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement
agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also
reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or
prosecution, or to suspend or terminate your membership in connection with any suspected illegal
activity. Additionally, we reserve the right to disclose the name of the registered owner and such owner’s
registered domain name registered to third parties and in our promotional materials.
Changing personal information
You have the ability to change or correct certain information in our records, such as your contact
information by signing in at http://www.domaincostclub.com and going to "My Account". You may
change this information at any time. If you have any questions about correcting or changing your
information, please contact us at abuse@domaincostclub.com.
